# **CURT POFF**

Portland Oregon (510) 229-7964 curt.poff@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/cpoff https://github.com/cpoff

# PERSONAL SUMMARY

I'm an experience producer, product and project manager. I bring 15 years of professional digital management experience to the table. Having just relocated and spent a year completing a dev bootcamp, I'm eager to land a position with a great company. Preferably one that put high value on learning and having fun.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

—HTML5, CSS, JavaScript (NodeJS, jQuery, Backbone), Bootstrap, Gulp, Heroku, PostgreSQL, RESTful web services, Express/Jade, text editors, packages/plug-ins/tools, TDD, Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop). Always eager to learn more.

—Lalso have extensive experience using open-source CMS (Drupal, WordPress). Ag

—I also have extensive experience using open-source CMS (Drupal, WordPress), Agile project management, and Git version control.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Developer - Full Stack Javascript Immersion program**

Portland Code School, May 2015 - Aug. 2015

—Over 500 hours of hands-on experience, building full-stack, responsive web applications with JavaScript using Node, MVC frameworks, and Test-Driven Development.

#### **Senior Producer - Interactive**

Walmart.com, San Bruno, Calif., Jan. 2013 - Nov. 2014

- —Senior member of the web producer team in the Creative department in the Walmart.com Customer Experience group. Delivered campaign assets and content in support of e-commerce goals.
- —Managed delivery of web assets and content through the entire creative process (brief presentation, look distribution, feedback collection, creative handoff) to further ecommerce goals.

# Sr. Web Producer, Sr. Project Manager, Product Manager

Macworld/PCWorld, San Francisco, Calif., Feb. 2005 - Jan. 2013

- —Managed all editorial products (home pages, index and article pages), publishing platform (CMS), and live events through the entire product lifecycle.
- —Coordinated and communicated efforts between marketing, editorial, development, and executive teams.
- Recipient of the 2008 Macworld/PCWorld Leadership Award.

### **Online Editor**

Arizona Republic, Phoenix Ariz., Aug. 2001 - Feb. 2005

- —Worked as news and sports content editor for azcentral.com, one of the most heavily trafficked newspaper Web sites in the country.
- —Edited and maintained the homepage and inside sections. Built slideshows and multimedia packages.

# **Web Producer**

KGW NewsChannel 8, Portland Ore., April 2000 - June 2001

- —Produced editorial content for kgw.com, 2001 winner of the Edward R. Murrow Award for best TV news Web site in the Pacific Northwest.
- —Created and edited content for all sections of kgw.com, including news, sports, business and technology, arts & entertainment.

# **EDUCATION**

B.S. in History, Portland State University Pragmatic Product Management Certificate of Completion, Portland Code School - Javascript Immersion